kingeshop.com 2019-06-24

# Private policy ecommerce solution provider, www.kingeshop.com

Policy on the Private Life

At KingEshop.com, we are anxious to ensure the confidentiality and the protection of personal information that you transmit to us. Please read what follows in order to obtain more details about our policy of confidentiality.

Protection of personal information

KingEshop.com installed safety measures to the fine point of technology to protect you from the loss or use the not - authorized information concerning you, like information on your credit card for example. The waiters of KingEshop.com use the technology SSL (Secure Socket Layers) which makes the transmission of information very sedentary.

On the other hand, there is always a risk in transmitting its personal information, thus KingEshop.com declines any responsibility if personal information is revealed, except in the event of negligence on behalf of KingEshop.com.

Collect and use of personal information

For accèder with the services, KingEshop.com requires that you transmit your name, your address, your address of email, your number of credit card and the other information considered to be relevant by KingEshop.com. You will have obligatorily to provide certain personal information to be able to use the service of KingEshop.com

We use this personal information to treat your orders, to deliver the products and services and finally to carry out the payment of the products and services to order. We also use this personal information to communicate with you if we have information to transmit to you concerning your orders or if we have new products, new services or new promotional offers.

Information which we pile up helps continuously to improve our virtual shop and our services. They also help us to detect and avoid the frauds or the abuses on our Internet site. Certain information is obligatory so that KingEshop.com can offer its services to you. We will indicate to you, if necessary, the fields considered as obligatory.

KingEshop.com wants that your personal information is precise and updates. With this intention, we provide you the occasion to modify or update your personal information (for the invoicing especially) in your account.

Divide and disclosure of personal information

KingEshop.com will not accept, under any condition nor with anyone, to sell or rent personal information which could identify you.

KingEshop.com could share your personal information with its partners only in the following cases:

-If we obtained your assent.

-If we must send your information to companies which work for the account of KingEshop.com to provide you a product or a service that you asked. (These companies do not have the right to use your personal information differently than to provide you the product or the service for which they are committed).

-If we must follow upon a subpoena court, an ordinance of the court or with a judicial body.

Bonds towards other Internet sites

The site of KingEshop.com contains bonds which redirect you towards other Internet sites, While clicking on one of these bonds you leave the site of KingEshop.com automatically, which wants to say that KingEshop.com does not have any more control on your personal information. You become then under the protection or the policy of confidentiality of the Internet site on which you clicked. We recommend to you to check well the policies of protection of the confidentiality of these sites before transmitting anything to them.

Cookies

The cookies are small textual files which will be transmitted to your computer so that KingEshop.com can recognize your navigator when you visit the site of KingEshop.com. The cookies are used to improve quality of our service by recording the preferences and the tendencies of our users. The cookies are not dangerous because they cannot extract information from your hard disk. This technology does not place necessarily personal information at the disposal of KingEshop.com. You can decontaminate the cookies by modifying the configuration of your computer, but without the cookies, you are likely to have problems to obtain services in certain Internet sites.

Modification of the policy of confidentiality

KingEshop.com reserves the right to modify its policy of confidentiality constantly. No change, even minor, which could involve a reduction in the protection of your personal information could not be done without your agreement. Any change with the policy of confidentiality of KingEshop.com will be published on this page. The more important changes will be announced in a particular way, for example, by sending an opinion by email to you.
